正如你知道的，我们希望改变的总比我们能做的多得多，
As you know, there's always more changes that we wish
如果我们只有一点时间。
we could do, if we just had a little more time.
我们将留下这些作为练习，如果你想
We're going to leave those as exercises to you, if you want to
继续改进。比如，为了简单起见，我们将全部平板的
keep polishing up. For example, for simplicity, we had all tablet
大小和方向用同样的布局。但是，7英寸的竖屏
sizes and orientations use the same layout. However, 7 inch portrait
将看起来比一个UI好得多。因此
would actually look better as a one pin UI. So you
你能够改变你的资源文件去使得7英寸竖屏使用
can modify your resource folders to make 7 inch portrait use
手机的布局。你也能够改变两个面板的行为
the phone layout. You can also tweak the two pane behavior
以至于today布局是默认被选中的当你第一次启动应用。
so that the today layout is auto selected when you first launch the
这里应该说today而不是显示完整的日期。
app. Also, this should just say today instead of having the full date. That
在你玩这个app时，
way, it'll look more like the other items. As you play around with the
你可以随意进行你认为能够增加用户体验的修改。
app, feel free to make changes you think would help improve the user experience.